[Get Started Today!
------------------](https://www.oxfordlearning.com/age-groups/)

    Oxford Learning is an award-winning member of the Canadian Franchise Association.

    * #### Join The Mailing List
        
        Javascript is required to submit this form.
        
        Subscribe

    Oxford Learning is an award-winning member of the Canadian Franchise Association.

Search

Search  

[Find Your Location

Call Us Today](https://www.oxfordlearning.com/locations/)

        #### By Age Groups

        #### Subject Areas

        #### Programs

        #### Specialty Services

        #### Join The Mailing List
        
        Javascript is required to submit this form.
        
        Subscribe
        
        #### Cognitive Learning

        #### Join The Mailing List
        
        Javascript is required to submit this form.
        
        Subscribe
        
        #### Company

        #### Join The Mailing List
        
        Javascript is required to submit this form.
        
        Subscribe
        
        #### Resources

    * Join The Mailing List

Search  

[Get Started Today!
------------------](https://www.oxfordlearning.com/age-groups/)

* Privacy Policy 

* * *

Privacy Policy
==============

### **This Privacy Policy was last modified on February 14, 2024.**

Oxford Learning® ’s Privacy Policy has been updating in accordance with new regulations set forth by the GDPR and new EU legislation surrounding data collection and privacy information.

Oxford Learning Centres, Inc. operates the website www.oxfordlearning.com. This page informs you of how we collect and use any personal information we receive from visitors to our website.

By using this website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Your personal information is used in conjunction with third-party websites for contact and ongoing marketing purposes such as emails, call tracking, marketing analytics, and CRM. By using this website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address, and phone number (“Personal Information”).

Our data forms will always disclose that information being entered is being collected for communication purposes. At any point in the data collection and communication process, users may unsubscribe or adjust their settings to disallow information collection.

#### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

#### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.  

If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. Instructions on how to disable cookies will vary according to what browser you are using. Here are some links to shutting off cookies on various popular browsers: [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?co=GENIE.Platform%253DDesktop&hl=en), [Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences), [Apple Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?locale=en_US).

#### DoubleClick Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Site. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Site or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [Google Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) page.

#### Google AdWords

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service within North America to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the site. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).

We use “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. All data over two years old is deleted. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use (as amended for government websites) and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.

Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the websites. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behaviour on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

#### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing materials such as postcards or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in any email we send.

#### Compliance With Laws

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Site.

#### Business Transaction

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

#### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Links To Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services. You may not link to our website without expressed permission from Oxford Learning Centres, Inc.

#### Children’s Privacy

Our Site does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a Child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.

#### Corporate Privacy Policy

Please [click here](https://www.oxfordlearning.com/corporate-privacy-policy/) to review our [Corporate Privacy Policy](https://www.oxfordlearning.com/corporate-privacy-policy/).

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about Oxford Learning’s Privacy Policy, please email [privacy@oxfordlearning.com](mailto:privacy@oxfordlearning.com).

**Privacy Officer Contact Information:**  
Chris Millar  
e: [privacy@oxfordlearning.com](mailto:privacy@oxfordlearning.com)  
p: 519.473.1207 x129

Join Oxford Learning's Mailing List
-----------------------------------

##### Get weekly learning tips and education articles delivered directly to your inbox. Sign up today!

Javascript is required to submit this form.

Subscribe

Search 

#### Corporate Office

747 Hyde Park Rd. Suite 230. London, ON N6H 3S3

Copyright © 2024 [Oxford Learning Centres](https://www.oxfordlearning.com/), All Rights Reserved.

Oxford Learning and the Oxford Learning Logo are registered trademarks of OX Royalties Limited Partnership, used under license.

[Monitored By:

](https://www.aodaonline.com/)[Web Design & Digital Marketing

](https://www.tbkcreative.com/)
